parkseed.com 2006-10-17

# Park Seed: Flower Bulbs, Seeds, Bulbs, Plants, Hydrangeas, Trees for you Gardens and Landscape.

PARKSEED.COM'S PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting our website! This website ("parkseed.com") is owned by George W. Park Seed Company, Inc. ("Park Seed"). It is our policy to protect your personal information and to use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please take a few moments to review our Privacy Policy. 

Information Collection and Use  
Park Seed asks you to provide certain personally identifiable information in order to use certain "Password Required" features and functions of the website. By providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of it, as described in this Privacy Policy. 

The information you provide may include information provided during the registration process, including contact information, such as your name, address and email address, and financial information, such as a credit card number, if you order products or services through the website. This information will be used to process your order and if necessary, to contact you regarding the status of your order. 

Information that you provide is the property of George W. Park Seed Company, Inc. All of the information that you provide may be used by Park Seed to better serve you. Park Seed may also use this information to contact you about new specials, catalogs, products and other opportunities. Ways we use information include: 

You can contact Park Seed directly with questions or comments regarding the services by using the parkseed.com contact inquiry form. This contact inquiry form asks you for certain identifying information so that Park Seed may respond to your inquiry. 

Park Seed may use your contact information to get in touch with you regarding the status of your registration or any orders you may place. You may also be contacted by us regarding additional services and features or requesting your feedback about your experience with parkseed.com. 

Parkseed.com may provide you with bulletin boards and chat rooms for your use. In the event you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information using such services, that information, along with any content in your communication or post, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Park Seed. Park Seed does not assume any duty to monitor or review the contents of any bulletin board or chat room. 

Where technically feasible, the domain names of visitors to parkseed.com are automatically recognized by our server. Park Seed may use this information to track the number of visitors to the parkseed.com website and to see which pages and services on parkseed.com are visited most often. 

The parkseed.com optional on-line survey generally asks for demographic information like your gender, age, etc. to help us get to know you and better understand your gardening needs. This data is used to personalize your experience at parkseed.com by displaying content according to your preferences. We hope this will enhance your experience with the parkseed.com site. 

Park Seed may provide links on parkseed.com to other sites of interest. Park Seed does not review or endorse the content of these sites or guarantee that they will abide by this Privacy Policy. Your use of such linked sites is subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies of the providers of those sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each website that collects identifying information. 

Please note that your use of the parkseed.com website and services is subject to Parkseed.com's Terms and Conditions.

Sharing Your Information  
Park Seed recognizes that gardeners may want products other than the high-quality seeds, plants, bulbs and accessories that we offer. Therefore, from time to time, Park Seed may make customer information available to other reputable companies whose products or services we think you might find interesting. Please remember that, although Park Seed endeavors to select only reputable companies who share our commitment to customer privacy, we are in no way responsible for the actions or policies of these other organizations. If you do not want to share your information with such other companies, click here now. 

Other Uses of Information  
The only other instances in which Park Seed discloses your identifying information to third parties are:  
when it is required by law; when it is necessary to distribute materials that you request; and when you expressly request that your information be disclosed.  

Business Transfers   
We may buy or sell operating divisions, companies or other business assets or be acquired by another company. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. 

Use of Cookies   
The use of cookies enables Park Seed to enhance your visits to the parkseed.com website. Cookies enable parkseed.com systems to recognize your browser and provide features that are tailored to your gardening needs. For example, cookies enable us to record the items in your shopping cart. Park Seed uses this information to monitor product sales which help us to plan future offerings. 

Accessing and Updating Your Information   
You can always choose not to provide information, to opt-out of receiving communications from us or to update your information at any time. Parkseed.com gives users the following options: 

  1. Use the "Change Preferences" feature after entering your member name and password to receive access to your account page. At this location, you can subscribe or unsubscribe from our e-mail newsletters and you can update any information that you have provided to us. 
  2. Click on the "Unsubscribe" link included at the bottom of each of our e-mails and follow the instructions on the web page. 
  3. Send an e-mail to our friendly Customer Service representatives at [info@parkscs.com](mailto:info@parkscs.com). 
  4. Call our Customer Service representatives toll free at (800) 213-0076. 
  5. Drop us a line. Send mail to the following postal address: Park Seed Company, 1 Parkton Avenue, Greenwood, SC 29647 

Security Measures   
We work hard to protect the security of your information by using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, the current standard for secure transactions over the Internet. There are some simple measures that you can take to promote protection of your information. First, to help protect the security of your account, do not share your password with others. Also, remember to “log-off” after using any of our on-line services when you have finished using the website. While Park Seed strives to protect your information by using SSL and through measures to protect our system, such security cannot be ensured. Consequently, Park Seed does not ensure or warrant the security of information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk. 

Encryption

**What is Encryption?**

Encryption is a process by which we use software to scramble sensitive information while it is in transit to Park Seed. 

Please take a moment to read about the steps that we have taken to help protect your information and make your online transmissions safer. We also invite you to review the steps you can take to help protect yourself further. 

**How Does Encryption Work?**

Encryption is based on a key that has two different parts. The public part and the private part. The public part of the key is distributed to those you want to communicate with. The private part is for the recipient's use only. 

When you send personal information to Parkseed.com, you use Park Seed's public key to encrypt your personal information. That means, if at any point during the transmission your information is intercepted, it is scrambled and very difficult to decrypt. Once Park Seed receives your encrypted personal information, we use the private part of our key to decode it. 

**What Kind of Encryption Software Does Park Seed Use?**

Park Seed currently uses the industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption. But we continue to keep up with the current technologies in order to provide the best security for our customers. 

**What Information Does Park Seed Encrypt?**

Park Seed encrypts all personal information you give us when you place an order online. Remember, if you feel uncomfortable providing any of this information online, please feel free to call one of our representatives at   
1-800-845-3369. 

**How Safe is Encryption Really?**

Providing encrypted information online is as safe as doing it over the phone. 

Privacy Policy Changes  
Parkseed.com may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to better serve you. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. 

For Further Information   
If you choose to visit parkseed.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy. If you have questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at:   
Park Seed Company, 1 Parkton Avenue, Greenwood, SC 29647 Phone: (800) 845-3369 Fax: (864) 941-4506 E-mail: [curator@parkscs.com](mailto:curator@parkscs.com)
